Guide to the Roy Eaton papers, 1860-2016 and undated. RL.11520
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1955-2014 and undated; 7
  - Audio Tape Reels, 1955-1991 and undated; 4
    - Original Maxwell House perking coffee pot; New Nestle Instant "Time", undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-249)
    - Presbytery Confrontation, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-250)
    - Presbytery Confrontation, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-251)
    - Quiet Please, 1968 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-252)
    - Quiet Please, 1968 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-253)
    - Roy Eaton Music--AIDS PSA, 1989 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-254)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Caffeine Free Diet Coke, 1990 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-255)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Caffeine Free Diet Coke, 1989 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-256)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Caffeine Free Diet Coke, 1989 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-257)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Carnation Milk International "Lullabies" 15 tracks, 1968 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-258)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Chrysler "Barber Shop", 1991 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-259)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Classic Malt Liquor 6 tracks, 1983 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-260)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Compilation 15 tracks 6:11, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-261)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Compilation 15 tracks 6:11, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-262)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Compilation 16 tracks 9:00, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-263)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Compilation 16 tracks 9:00, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-264)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo reel 12 tracks, 1983 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-265)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo reel 2, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-266)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo reel 3, 1983 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-267)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo reel 11 tracks 6:20, 1985 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-268)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Diet Coke, 1989 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-269)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Diet Coke, 1989 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-270)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Hardee's demos, 1982 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-271)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Jingle reel 9 tracks, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-272)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Jingle reel 9 tracks, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-273)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Kentucky Fried Chicken "New Spicy Crispy", 1982 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-274)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Lite Brite, 1988 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-275)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Lite Brite, 1988 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-276)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Presentation reel new test, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-277)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Willie Strickland demo 12 tracks, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-278)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Willie Strickland demo 12 tracks, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-279)
    - Roy Eaton performance :60, 1992 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-280)
    - Sing a Song (Susan Holloran), 1979 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-281)
    - Songs by Susan Ring 7 tracks, 1979 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-282)
    - This Man Said, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-283)
    - This Man Said remix, 1972 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-284)
    - This Man Said, 1970 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-285)
    - To Be Free (Nick Hollander), undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-286)
    - Too Serious Too Soon (Neil Shephard), undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-287)
    - Wine 3 tracks (Night Train), 1975 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-288)
    - Woman in Business, 1977 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-289)
    - Woman in Business, 1977 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-290)
    - Won't You Be My Girl (Jacques Roc), 1980 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-291)
    - Your Mother instrumental mix, 1977 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-292)
    - Your Mother, 1977 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-293)
    - Your Mother, undated (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-294)
    - Your Mother, 1977 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-295)
    - Your Mother, 1977 (Box AV24, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-296)
    - Roy Eaton piano--The Meditative Chopin reel 1 of 2, 1986 (Box AV25, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-297)
    - Roy Eaton piano--The Meditative Chopin reel 2 of 2, 1986 (Box AV25, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-298)
  - Audio Cassette Tapes, 1974-1996 and undated; 5
    - Ariel Joseph/Nick Cosco--Never Isn't Never, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-001)
    - Barry Manilow--I Am Your Child, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-002)
    - Fay Tishman--American Dream, 1979 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-003)
    - Fred Lederman/Stephen Lemberg--Bonjour Reaction spots, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-004)
    - Gallo Winery--Night Train "Party Train", undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-005)
    - Gandharva Veda Music, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-006)
    - Gil Music--Feels So Nice; Make It Last, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-007)
    - Glory Foods Introductory Radio Campaign, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-008)
    - John Strickland--Whatever Is, Is Best, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-009)
    - Juliette McGinnis (?)--Environment meditations, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-010)
    - Maharishi Ayur-Veda Pulse Assessment Program, 1990 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-011)
    - Neil Shepherd--Garden of Delight, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-012)
    - Neil Shepherd--Songs, 1979 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-013)
      Touch Me; No Turning Back Tonight; Too Serious Too Soon; Music Is Love
    - Open Door--Friendship; Love, 1979 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-014)
    - Phil Dority broadcast--Telecommunications Consumer Coalition, 1982 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-015)
    - Relaxation demo, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-016)
    - Susan Holloran--Sing a Song, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-017)
    - Suzanne Fazio--Songs, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-018)
      Am I Scared; You Are Not Alone; I Know What I Want; You Danced Away With My Heart; Sometimes Someone
    - Talent--Try Me; Shape Some show #1, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-019)
    - Ted Rosenthal--The Survivor, 1993 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-020)
    - Tina Fabrik--Songs, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-021)
      Mr. Disco Man; It's Hard to Leave While the Music's Playing; You Turn On My Music
    - Tomo master tape, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-022)
    - Winter-Gold--A Strong Hit, 1979 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-023)
    - Voices of the 20s, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-024)
    - Yavapai Indian, 1992 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-025)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Air Force "Aim High" demo, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-026)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Anne Bryant composer, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-027)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Buried Bird, 1984 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-028)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Chrysler "Killer Joe", 1989 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-029)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Coca-Cola Classic Cosby zydeco :30, 1989 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-030)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Dark and Lovely, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-031)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo 12 tracks 7:00, 1984 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-032)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo 11 tracks 6:20, 1985 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-033)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo 15 tracks 9:00, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-034)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-035)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo #1, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-036)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo, 1983 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-037)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo, 1983 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-038)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo 16 tracks 9:00, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-039)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo 9 tracks, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-040)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo, 1991 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-041)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Demo reel 1 16 tracks 9:00, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-042)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Disco Freak copy remix 2, 1979 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-043)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Disco Freak copy remix 2, 1979 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-044)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Disco Freak remix, 1979 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-045)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Gotta Be the Best, 1982 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-046)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Gwen Conley, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-047)
      Let the Music Play; Love Will Come Again
    - Roy Eaton Music--Gwen Conley, 1979 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-048)
      Love Will Come Again; Disco Freak
    - Roy Eaton Music--Gwen Conley, 1979 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-049)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Hanes Underwear for Men, 1983 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-050)
      Futterman/Abbott; Ted Michaels; Rick Brinkman; Abby Gesben
    - Roy Eaton Music--Infinity Factory 14 tracks, 1977 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-051)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Jacques Roc, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-052)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Jazz Demo, 1992 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-053)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Jazz scoring Benny Golson, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-054)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Jingle demo, 1988 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-055)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Jingles, 1990 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-056)
      Jimmy Ryan (Pringles, Doritos, Turtle Wax, Colt 45); Micki Grant (Caffeine Free Diet Coke; Air Force); Rich Meitin (Sneaker Tamers, Wachovia); Ken Williams (NFL on TNT); Tamara Kline (Battle Ball, ABC News)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Jingles/Scoring, 1988 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-057)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Jingles new master, 1990 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-058)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Just for Men compilation, 1989-1993 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-059)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Just for Men radio, 1993 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-060)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Let the Music Play/I'm a Disco Freak, 1979 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-061)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Love Will Come Again/Disco Freak rough mix, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-062)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Malcolm Dodds demo, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-063)
      Homeless; Sweet Lady; I Love You in the Morning; You; I Want to Make You Glad; If I Could Just Forget You
    - Roy Eaton Music--Meisoh Fashion Show/Nisei Fashions, 1984 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-064)
    - Roy Eaton Music--MSR commercial music, 1980 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-065)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Music demo, 1992 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-066)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Music demo, 1992 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-067)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Newsweek "Commitment", 1983 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-068)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Night Beat, 1985 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-069)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Pantene shampoo, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-070)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Parking Lot, 1992 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-071)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Radio, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-072)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Roy Eaton announcer, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-073)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Roy Eaton voiceover: Habitat; Big Brother, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-074)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Rich Meitin contemporary jazz reel, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-075)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Schlitz Classic Malt Liquor, 1984 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-076)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Scoring demo, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-077)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Scoring demo, 1989 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-078)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Scoring demo, undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-079)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Scoring master, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-080)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Scoring reel, 1988 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-081)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Alaska (Ktoo, Juneau), 1988 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-082)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Alaska promo, 1988 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-083)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Albany concert, 1990 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-084)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Albany; Hailstork Trio, 1990 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-085)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Albany; Israel AME Zion Church, 1990 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-086)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Alice Tully Hall, 1987 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-087)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Alice Tully Hall, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-088)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Alice Tully Hall: Meditative Chopin, 1986 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-089)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Alice Tully Hall: Meditative Chopin, 1986 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-090)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Alice Tully Hall, 1986 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-091)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Alice Tully Hall, 1987 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-092)
    - Roy Eaton performance--All Chopin program, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-093)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Amsterdam House recital, 1987 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-094)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Bob Sherman WQXR, 1987 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-095)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Chopin concerto, Richman H.S., 1988 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-096)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Chopin, Bach recital, 1972 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-097)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Chopin rehearsal, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-098)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Chopin part 2, 1982 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-099)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Barcarolle, Improvisations, 1974 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-100)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Columbia Presbyterian Hospital with Tommy Goodman, Don Segal, 1980 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-101)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Concert, Bach and Beethoven program, 1972 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-102)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Chopin, Schubert, 1974 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-103)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Concert part 1: Joplin, Debussy, Bach, 1975 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-104)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Concert part 2: Chopin, 1975 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-105)
    - Eric Butterworth, 1976 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-106)
    - Eric Butterworth, 1976 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-107)
    - Eric Butterworth, 1976 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-108)
    - Eric Butterworth, 1976 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-109)
    - Eric Butterworth, 1976 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-110)
    - Eric Butterworth, 1976 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-111)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Unity Retreat concert, 1977 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-112)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Alice Tully Hall, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-113)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Alice Tully Hall, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-114)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Debussy Impressions, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-115)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Debussy Impressions rough, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-116)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Debussy Impressions rough, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-117)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Eaton roots piano concert, 1977 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-118)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Fine Arts Symphony, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-119)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Fine Arts Symphony, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-120)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Fire Island: The Meditative Chopin, 1985 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-121)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Lake Forest, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-122)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Gateways Music Festival, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-123)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Harlem Piano Music USA, 1993 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-124)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Harlem Piano Music USA, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-125)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Improvisation, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-126)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Hollis, 1976 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-127)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Hollis, 1976 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-128)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Hollis, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-129)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Joplin #4, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-130)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Joplin #4, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-131)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Jurow/Eaton part 1, 1978 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-132)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Jurow/Eaton part 2, 1978 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-133)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Lanzihuus Suhr concert (Meditative Chopin), 1984 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-134)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Lanzihuus Suhr concert (Meditative Chopin), 1984 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-135)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Lanzihuus Suhr concert (Meditative Chopin), 1985 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-136)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Lanzihuus Suhr concert (Meditative Chopin), 1985 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-137)
    - Roy Eaton performance--L'Ensemble, 1990 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-138)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin, 1986 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-139)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-140)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin Vol. 2, 1985 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-141)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin, 1986 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-142)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-143)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin, 1986 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-144)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin, St. Peter Church, 1981 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-145)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin (Commercial release), 1996 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-146)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin Vol. 2 (Commercial release), 1989 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-147)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin Vol. 2, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-148)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin Vol. 2, 1985 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-149)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meditative Chopin, Universalist Church, 1983 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-150)
    - Roy Eaton performance--MIU concert, 1988 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-151)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Moscow debut, Meditative Chopin, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-152)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Moscow; Institut Gnessink, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-153)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Moscow, Gelikon Theatre, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-154)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Peru (Lima), Chopin F minor concerto, 1981 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-155)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Peru (Lima), Orquesta Sinfonica Nacional, Chopin F minor concerto, 1981 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-156)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Peru (Lima), Chopin F minor concerto, 1981 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-157)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Peru (Lima), recital debut, Institut Cultural Peruano, all Chopin, 1981 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-158)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Peru (Lima), 1981 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-159)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano, undated (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-160)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano, 1988 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-161)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano: Chopin, Gershwin, 1985 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-162)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano part 1 (Hollis, NY): Chopin, Debussy, 1983 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-163)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano part 2 (Hollis, NY): Debussy, Joplin, 1983 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-164)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital, 1977 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-165)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-166)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano: Chopin, 1980 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-167)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano: Mozart, Beethoven, Schumann, Joplin, 1980 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-168)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano, 1991 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-169)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Roy Eaton 10/22/92 AM, 1992 (Box AV27, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-170)
    - Roy Eaton performance--St. James recital, 1975 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-171)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital, Bach program (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-172)
    - Roy Eaton performance--(Isadora) Duncan recital, 1982 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-173)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Carnegie recital with dancers "The Art of Isadora", 1982 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-174)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital; Bach, Mozart, Chopin, Liszt, Joplin, Chopin, 1977 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-175)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital: Bach, Mozart, Hailstork, Chopin, 1992 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-176)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital: Bach, Mozart, Hailstork, Chopin, 1992 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-177)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital: Liszt, Schubert, Chopin, 1971 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-178)
    - Roy Eaton performance--"Generation", undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-179)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Rehearsal tape 1, 1987 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-180)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Rehearsal tape 3, 1987 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-181)
    - Roy Eaton performance--RMAA band concert, 1979 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-182)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Saturday, undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-183)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Schaffthausen Rathauslaube, 1988 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-184)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Solo piano selections, undated (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-185)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Roy plays Meditative concert part 1, 1976 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-186)
    - Roy Eaton performance--The Twenties record 3 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-187)
    - Roy Eaton performance--WNCN promotion, 1987 (Box AV28, Audio-cassette RL11520-CAS-188)
    - Ad Council--Drunk Driving PSA for Leber Katz Partners, 1983 (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-001)
      Crashing Glasses :30, :10
  - Video Tapes, 1976-2007 and undated; 6
    - Ad Council--Drunk Driving PSA for Leber Katz Partners, undated (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-002)
      Christmas Wreath :10
    - Ad Council--Drunk Driving PSA for Leber Katz Partners, 1984 (Box AV29, Video-cassette RL11520-UMATIC-003)
      Skeleton :10, :30